CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE
BY CAPITAL CITIES/ABC. INC.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
LAST CARD.
AN ACE HELPS LOW.
KING. NO HELP.
5. PAIR UP.
DEALER GETS 4.
REMEMBER THOSE SWEAT SUITS
WE SAW FOR 19 BUCKS?
RODBELL'S HAS THEM FOR $14.99.
RODBELL'S IS THE
ONLY PLACE IN AMERICA
WHERE YOU CAN GET
THONGS ALL YEAR ROUND.
DARLENE. YOU DIDN'T ANTE.
SORRY. DAD.
WE BET $50.000.
I CALL.
IT'S NOT YOUR TURN.
YEAH. BUT IT'S MY HOUSE.
WE PLAYING OR
SHOOTING THE BREEZE?
SHOOTING THE BREEZE.
OK. THE PORTCHESTER GAME.
LAST GAME OF MY SENIOR YEAR.
ONE MINUTE TO GO.
LET'S PLAY POKER.
WE'RE SHOOTING THE BREEZE.
WE KNOW THIS STORY.
THIS TIME... THE REFEREE'S SIDE.
I GOT A PAIR.
SO DO I.
YEAH. BUT ROSEANNE'S
ARE SHOWING.
YOU THINK WE DON'T GET
YOUR CORNY LITTLE SEX JOKES.
HEY. YOU KIDS ARE OUR
CORNY LITTLE SEX JOKES.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
CHEESE IT. THE FUZZ.
HIDE THE CARDS AND THE CHIPS.
I THINK IT'S TIME WE TAUGHT D.J.
HOW TO PLAY 52-CARD PICKUP.
AAH.
TA-DA!
DAD. WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I CAME TO SEE MY
SWEET LITTLE KAPUTCHKA.
AL!
HEY. DANNY.
DAD!
OH. MY GOSH!
IS EVERYTHING OK?
FINE. FINE.
WHERE'S GRANDMA?
THERE SHE IS NOW.
HELLO.
MA!
MOM. HI.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
DOING IN LANFORD?
THIS MORNING I ASKED YOUR MOTHER
WHAT SHE WANTED TO DO.
SO WE TOOK A LITTLE RIDE.
250 MILES ISN'T A LITTLE DRIVE.
ESPECIALLY WHEN
YOU HAVE A WOMAN.
WHO WHENEVER A CAR PASSES.
SAYS. "I WONDER
WHERE THEY'RE GOING."
BOY. SHE'S GOT PROBLEMS.
WHY DIDN'T YOU CALL?
I DID. BUT YOUR LINE WAS BUSY.
I TRIED YOUR SISTER.
I COULDN'T GET HER.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
SOMETHING WAS WRONG.
GOD KNOWS SHE'D NEVER TELL ME.
MY APARTMENT'S
GETTING FUMIGATED.
FUMIGATED FOR WHAT.
THOSE LOUSES YOU GO OUT WITH?
THEY'RE BACK.
WE NEED MILK?
WE NEED EGGS?
BULLETS?
COME ON. DAN. LET'S JUST
TRY TO GET THROUGH THIS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
I CAN'T SLEEP.
GRANDPA'S IN THE BATHROOM
MAKING THOSE GAGGING NOISES.
EU!
HOW LONG'S HE BEEN IN THERE?
AT LEAST HALF AN HOUR.
HE'S PROBABLY GOT
IT ALL UP BY NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU GO BACK TO BED?
HE'S REALLY DRIVING ME CRAZY.
IF HE SAYS. "PULL MY FINGER"
ONE MORE TIME...
WELL. NOW YOU KNOW
WHERE I GET MY SMART.
SOPHISTICATED WIT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
MAN RAISED YOU.
NOW YOU KNOW WHY I
MARRIED YOU SO YOUNG.
YOU WERE MADLY IN LOVE.
WITH THE IDEA OF
GETTING OUT OF MY HOUSE.
IS THERE A PLACE IN
HERE TO SIT DOWN?
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
ONE OF THESE THINGS
WE CALL CHAIRS?
WE SIT IN THEM FREQUENTLY.
WHAT KIND OF LIST IS HE MAKING?
A HIT LIST.
HE'S GOING OUT TO THE STORE.
DON'T GET ANYTHING
SPECIAL FOR ME.
BUT YOUR FATHER'S
DIET IS LOW SODIUM.
LOW FAT. AND HIGH FIBER.
WHY DON'T WE JUST
GET HIM SOME WOOD?
HE CAN PUT MUSTARD ON IT.
MUSTARD'S HIGH IN FAT.
MANY PEOPLE DON'T KNOW THAT.
MANY PEOPLE DON'T CARE.
I DO.
BUT DOGGONE IT. I GOT TO GO.
HE'S NOT WORKING. IS HE?
HE'S WORKING.
I'M GLAD BECAUSE
YOUR FATHER WORRIES.
ESPECIALLY ABOUT YOUR SISTER.
HE DOESN'T HAVE TO WORRY.
WELL. SOMEBODY HAS TO.
SHE'S 32.
SHE'S UNMARRIED.
HEAVEN FORBID SHE TURNS
OUT TO BE LIKE YOUR AUNT DALE
WHO TEACHES P.E.
SPEAKING OF AUNT DALE.
HOW IS UNCLE SHIRLEY?
ALSO. YOUR FATHER'S CONCERNED
BECAUSE YOUR SISTER
LIVES IN A BUILDING
THAT NEEDS TO BE FUMIGATED.
BUT I'M HER MOTHER.
IT'S NOT MY JOB TO
TELL HER WHAT TO DO.
BUT IT'S YOUR JOB
TO TELL ME TO TELL
HER WHAT TO DO.
YES. I'M SURE PETUNIAS
ARE PERENNIALS.
JACKIE. MOM WAS JUST
TALKING ABOUT YOU.
NOW YOU GET TO LISTEN
WHILE SHE TALKS ABOUT ME.
WE GOING TO TALK ABOUT ROSEANNE?
CERTAINLY NOT.
IT'S JUST THAT YOUR
FATHER'S WORRIED ABOUT HER.
SHE SEEMS SO TIRED.
MOM. YOU'VE BEEN HERE A
GRAND TOTAL OF ONE HOUR.
HOW DO YOU KNOW
HOW TIRED SHE IS?
A MOTHER KNOWS.
GRANTED IT WAS A
DIFFERENT GENERATION.
BUT YOUR FATHER WOULD HAVE DIED
BEFORE HE MADE ME WORK.
DAN DOESN'T MAKE ROSEANNE WORK.
THAT'S WHAT SHE TELLS YOU.
YOU'RE NOT MARRIED. YOU
DON'T KNOW THESE THINGS.
WHAT DID YOU FIND OUT ABOUT ME?
YOU'RE VERY TIRED.
HEY. MA. IS TWO BLANKETS ENOUGH?
TWO'S FINE...
IF THAT'S ALL YOU HAVE.
I HAVE MORE. HOW
MANY WOULD YOU LIKE?
WHAT DID YOUR FATHER SAY?
HE SAYS HE'LL BE SLEEPING
IN THE DRIVEWAY NAKED.
HOW MANY BLANKETS DO YOU WANT?
IF YOU HAVE TWO.
TWO'S FINE.
I'M CLOSE TO THE EDGE.
IF I GO OVER. YOU'RE
COMING WITH ME.
SHE DOES HAVE A WAY ABOUT HER.
IF SHE WANTS TO RAG ON YOU.
WHY DOESN'T SHE JUST TELL YOU?
I'M SICK OF THESE
BEHIND-THE-BACK CONVERSATIONS.
LIKE THE ONE WE'RE HAVING
ABOUT MOM RIGHT NOW?
YEAH. YEAH.
WHY SHOULD I HAVE TO
DEFEND THE GUYS YOU DATE?
YOU SHOULDN'T.
AND I'M TIRED OF
EXPLAINING TO HER
WHY YOUR HOUSE IS
SO FILTHY ALL THE TIME.
YEAH. THAT'S MY BUSINESS.
SHE JUST DOESN'T LET UP.
SHE'S GOING TO LET UP
BECAUSE I'M GOING
TO LAY INTO HER.
THAT WOMAN'S NOT QUALIFIED
TO JUDGE ANYBODY'S LIFE.
MA?
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH ALREADY.
WE GOT TO DO THIS.
I FOUND THIS UNDER
YOUR SISTER'S SOFA.
MOM. WHY ARE YOU
GIVING IT TO ME?
IT'S HER POTATO CHIPS. HER SOFA.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE THE WAY
ROSEANNE KEEPS
HOUSE. TALK TO ROSEANNE.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE
THE WAY I RUN MY LIFE.
TALK TO ME ABOUT
IT. NOT TO ROSEANNE.
WE'RE SICK OF THE
WAY YOU MANIPULATE US.
IS THAT SO. ROSEANNE?
YEAH.
RIGHT?
WELL. MAYBE MANIPULATE'S
KIND OF A HARSH WORD
TO USE HERE.
I JUST THINK WHAT JACKIE MEANS.
WHAT SHE'S TRYING TO SAY.
IS THAT WE WISH
YOU WOULD DEAL WITH US
IN A MORE DIRECT MANNER.
NO. THAT'S NOT WHAT
JACKIE'S TRYING TO SAY.
WHERE THE HELL WERE YOU
FIVE MINUTES AGO?
WHERE DO YOU WANT THIS COT?
SET UP ON A BEACH IN CANCUN.
D.J.!
WHAT?
GO UP TO BED NOW.
OK.
I'LL GET SOME SHEETS. MOM.
YOU REALLY SHOULD TURN
YOUR MATTRESS MORE OFTEN.
WHERE WILL YOU SLEEP?
ANYWHERE'S OK WITH ME.
HEY. I DON'T SLEEP ANYWHERE.
HELL. THESE... THESE
COTS ARE PRETTY NICE.
I'M SURE THEY DON'T
WANT TO SLEEP ON COTS.
WHAT DID WE DO LAST TIME?
LAST TIME? I'VE COMPLETELY
BLOCKED IT OUT OF MY MIND.
YOU GUYS DON'T MIND
SLEEPING ON COTS?
I CAN SLEEP ANYWHERE.
TAKE OUR BED. WE'LL
SLEEP ON THE COTS.
I CAN'T SLEEP ON THESE THINGS.
LAST TIME. GRANDMA AND GRANDPA
SLEPT UP IN OUR ROOM.
I WANT TO SLEEP
ON A SLEEPING BAG.
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE DID.
I'M PARTICULAR
ABOUT WHERE I SLEEP.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I'LL TELL YOU
SOMETHING ABOUT ME.
I'LL NEVER SLEEP IN A
COMMUNIST COUNTRY.
I'LL VISIT ONE DURING THE DAY.
BUT I'LL NEVER SLEEP IN ONE.
WELL. GOD BLESS AMERICA.
CAN I SLEEP IN A SLEEPING BAG?
NO. GO.
HOW ABOUT WHAT I SAID?
WHICH WAS?
FORGET IT.
LET'S NOT FUSS ABOUT THIS.
WE CAN SLEEP ANYWHERE.
GRANDMA AND
GRANDPA HAD OUR ROOM.
THIS COT STILL SMELLS
FROM THE DEAD
PIGEON WE FOUND IN IT.
DARLENE.
D.J. AND I SLEPT ON THE FLOOR.
MOM AND DAD HAD D.J.'s BED.
BUT IT'S TOO SMALL.
JACKIE. YOU WERE NOT EVEN HERE.
TEMPER. TEMPER.
HOW COME I CAN REMEMBER IT?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE TOTAL RECALL
OF ALL THINGS IMAGINARY.
GIRLS. GIRLS.
LET'S BE LADIES. SHALL WE?
CAN WE COME TO SOME CONCLUSION?
I'LL GIVE YOU A CONCLUSION.
JACKIE. SLEEP IN D.J.'s BED.
D.J.. SLEEP IN A SLEEPING BAG!
GIRLS. GIRLS. LET'S
BE LITTLE LADIES
AND SLEEP IN YOUR OWN BED.
YOU TAKE ME AND DAN'S ROOM.
I'M GOING TO SLEEP ON THE COT.
AND SO IS MR. FLEXIBLE.
HOPEFULLY WE WON'T
HAVE THIS CONFUSION
ONCE YOUR FATHER
AND I HAVE A PLACE
RIGHT HERE IN LANFORD.
SLEEP TIGHT. EVERYONE.
NIGHTIE-NIGHT.
DAN. ARE YOU SLEEPING?
LIKE A BABY.
THE FACT THAT IT'S 4:30 A.M.
AND I HAVE A SPRING
IN MY PANCREAS
ISN'T KEEPING ME AWAKE
THE LEAST LITTLE BIT.
IF MY PARENTS MOVE TO LANFORD.
I'LL BE SLEEPING ON A COT
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE
BECAUSE I'LL BE IN PRISON
FOR BLOWING THEM AWAY.
HONEY. HONEY. BE REALISTIC.
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW TO USE A GUN.
I'LL DO IT.
SERIOUSLY. DAN. WHAT
ARE WE GOING TO DO?
WELL. I'D SAY.
"LET'S SLEEP ON IT."
BUT WHO CAN SLEEP?
IF YOU COULD STAND
UP TO YOUR PARENTS.
WE WOULDN'T BE LYING HERE.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
I'M WARNING YOU. THAT
FIREPLACE POKER'S WITHIN REACH.
BABY. LET'S NOT GET
INTO THIS RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE IT'S NOT MY WARPED.
PSYCHOTIC. NEUROTIC PARENTS
LAYING IN MY BED.
I'M GOING TO SIT ON THE PORCH.
HONEY. HONEY.
HONEY. LET'S NOT DO
THIS TO EACH OTHER.
I'M SORRY. I'M JUST ANGRY
'CAUSE I HAVEN'T SLEPT.
WE GOT A COUPLE
HOURS LEFT TILL DAYLIGHT.
LET'S JUST TRY TO
SALVAGE SOME SLEEP.
[SNORTING]
[GAGGING]
AL?
AL.
OH.
I'M JUST GOING
TO MAKE YOUR FATHER BREAKFAST.
HE ALWAYS GETS UP AT 4:30.
GO BACK TO SLEEP.
FEEL LIKE MAKING LOVE?
I JUST WANT TO KNOW WHERE
YOU KEEP YOUR CITRUS FRUIT.
THERE'S SOME
STRAWBERRY POP TARTS
IN THE FRIDGE.
YOUR FATHER NEEDS TO
HAVE A PIECE OF CITRUS FRUIT.
THERE'S AN ORANGE
UNDER THE DRYER.
DAN SHOULDN'T
SLEEP ON HIS LEFT SIDE.
IT'S BAD FOR THE HEART.
SO'S A RUSTY SPIKE.
THIS IS NUTS.
I GOT A NEW JOB TO START TODAY.
I'VE GOT TO GO TO WORK. TOO.
THEN TELL MA AND
PA KETTLE TO SHUT UP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP SO EARLY?
YOU GOT ANY KLEENEX?
USE DAN'S BOWLING SHIRT.
THANKS. YOU'RE WELCOME.
THANKS. THIS IS THE BEST
ROOM IN YOUR HOUSE.
YEAH. 'CAUSE MOM
AND DAD AREN'T IN IT.
THIS IS OUR SANCTUARY FROM THEM.
DON'T COUNT ON IT.
SHE'LL FIGURE OUT
SOME WAY TO GET IN.
THEN YOU CAN STAND
UP TO HER LIKE BEFORE.
I SAID TO YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
"BEVERLY..." I CALL HER BEVERLY
BECAUSE THAT'S HER NAME.
I SAID. "BEVERLY. THIS YEAR
"I'M PAYING MORE ATTENTION
TO MY STABLE AND HORSES."
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY
HORSES. GRANDPA.
'CAUSE I DON'T HAVE A STABLE.
PULL MY FINGER. KID.
DON'T.
I'M SORRY. WHAT WERE YOU SAYING?
OH. I'M FINISHED.
ARE YOU GUYS GETTING
READY FOR SCHOOL?
YEAH. AND WE'RE
REALLY EXCITED ABOUT IT.
THAT'S GREAT.
THEY'RE REALLY DOING
GREAT IN SCHOOL.
AL WAS ALWAYS CONCERNED
WITH THE CHILDREN'S EDUCATION.
HE WAS SOME FATHER.
WHAT IS IT YOU
ALWAYS USED TO SAY?
YOU CAN LEAD A HORSE TO WATER.
BUT YOU CAN'T MAKE HIM THINK.
YOU USED TO SAY THAT...
AND YOU STOPPED SAYING THAT?
HE USED TO SAY THAT.
AND HE DOESN'T SAY IT ANYMORE.
HE USED TO SAY.
"YOU CAN LEAD A HORSE TO WATER.
BUT YOU CAN'T MAKE HIM THINK."
AND HE DOESN'T SAY IT ANYMORE.
I HAVEN'T SLEPT.
HOW DID WE GROW UP NORMAL?
'CAUSE YOU HAD ME
TO SAVE YOUR BUTT.
I RECALL I DID A LITTLE
BUTT-SAVING FOR YOU. TOO.
WE'RE ONLY SANE TODAY
BECAUSE WE KEPT
EACH OTHER THAT WAY.
WE PROTECTED EACH OTHER
FROM MR. AND MRS.
TOTAL INSANITY.
YEAH. LIKE WHEN YOU
WERE IN EIGHTH GRADE
AND YOU DATED THAT
40-YEAR-OLD GUY.
HE WAS NOT 40.
HE WAS THE ONLY GUY
AT YOUR FRESHMAN DANCE
WEARING A TOUPEE.
I TOLD MOM HE WAS YOUR TUTOR.
AND I TAUGHT HIM MORE.
THAT'S THE WAY IT GOES.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS
THAT MOM AND DAD
ARE JUST SO OUT THERE.
WELL. YOU KNOW. IT'S
NOT ALL THEIR FAULT.
WE SHOULD SHOW THEM
A LITTLE COMPASSION.
WELL. HERE WE GO AGAIN.
CHECK IN YOUR
BACKBONE AT THE DOOR.
WELL. FINE. YOU BLAME
YOUR WHOLE LIFE ON THEM.
ROSEANNE. YOU TURN INTO A ROBOT
EVERY TIME MOM AND
DAD COME AROUND.
AND I'M SICK OF IT.
PEOPLE WHO LIVE IN
COCKROACH-INFESTED APARTMENTS
SHOULD NOT THROW STONES.
YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO
GET YOUR OWN WAY.
IT HAS TO BE MY WAY
WHEN YOU'RE IN MY BATHROOM
AFTER MY PARENTS
CAME OVER TO MY HOUSE...
NOW THEY'RE YOUR PARENTS!
IF YOU WANT THEM.
FINE. YOU HAVE THEM!
TELL ME WHEN IT'S
THEIR ANNIVERSARY
AND YOU LET THEM
STAY AT YOUR HOUSE
AND DECIMATE YOUR FAMILY.
WHICH YOU DON'T HAVE
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T
CONCENTRATE ON NOTHING LONGER
THAN IT TAKES TO CHUG A BEER.
DON'T GIVE ME THAT WOUNDED LOOK
BECAUSE THAT ONLY
WORKS ON GUYS NAMED MIKE.
VERY DRAMATIC. ROSEANNE.
OH. SO NOW YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO TALK TO ME.
GOD. WOULD I LOVE
TO THROW A HAMMER
THROUGH A PLATE GLASS WINDOW.
HER MAJESTY'S NOT
SPEAKING TO ANYBODY TODAY.
HEY. JACKIE. WHO EVEN ASKED YOU?
I'M A PART OF THIS FAMILY.
YEAH. WHEN YOUR HAMPER'S FULL.
I'VE BEEN IN THIS FAMILY
LONGER THAN YOU.
BOY. THAT'S SOMETHING
TO BE PROUD OF.
I SAW A WHOLE THING
ABOUT THIS ON OPRAH.
AND WE'RE JUST LIKE THAT.
WE ARE A DYSFUNCTIONAL FAMILY!
AAH!
THERE. THAT WILL NEVER COME OUT.
I LEARNED THAT WHILE
I WAS A PARATROOPER.
I WONDER HOW MANY TIMES
HE LANDED ON HIS HEAD.
THANKS. GRAMPS.
BYE. GRAM.
BYE. BECKY.
GOODBYE. DEAR.
GRANDPA SAID HE'D BUY
ME A HORSE NEXT YEAR.
YEAH. WELL. GRANDPA'S
SADDLE'S ON TOO TIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAKING BREAKFAST FOR MY KIDS.
I ALREADY MADE THEM BREAKFAST.
GO TO SCHOOL. THEN.
BYE.
BYE. KIDS.
SHE MADE THEM BREAKFAST.
CEREAL WITH
CHOCOLATE CHIP COOKIES.
YOUR FATHER GAVE THEM COOKIES.
EATING THEM NOW OR LATER.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
YOU WANT TO KNOW THE DIFFERENCE?
THE DIFFERENCE IS YOU
SHOW UP AT MY DOOR
UNANNOUNCED. UNINVITED.
YOU JUST WORK
EVERYBODY UP INTO A FRENZY
UNTIL WE'RE READY
TO KILL EACH OTHER!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE'RE HAVING BREAKFAST.
IF YOU MOVE TO LANFORD.
YOU'LL HAVE TO MOVE TO
THE OTHER SIDE OF TOWN.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS FOREVER.
WHO'S MOVING TO LANFORD?
YOU ARE.
YOU SAID SO LAST NIGHT.
WE'RE NEVER GOING
TO MOVE INTO LANFORD.
WE WERE JUST THINKING.
WE WERE JUST TALKING.
WHY DO YOU TAKE
EVERYTHING SO SERIOUSLY?
SO YOU'RE NOT MOVING?
NO. IN FACT. WE'VE GOT TO GO.
WE'RE GOING TO
SEE COUSIN SIDNEY.
HE HAD GUM SURGERY.
I'M GOING TO BUY HIM
SOME ROCK CANDY.
WELL. IT'S A SHAME YOU
COULDN'T HAVE STAYED LONGER.
DAN. DO YOU REALLY MEAN THAT?
HEY. IF YOU DON'T THINK
YOUR LEAVING WILL
AFFECT EVERYBODY.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
OH. THAT'S SO SWEET.
AL. DID YOU HEAR THAT?
YEAH. I'D GIVE HIM A BIG KISS...
OH...
IF I LIKED BOYS.
OH. MOM. I'M REALLY
GOING TO MISS YOU.
ME. TOO.
OH...
THIS HAS BEEN A GREAT VISIT.
OH. THIS HAS BEEN
A WONDERFUL VISIT.
LET ME DO IT AGAIN.
DID YOU WASH YOUR HANDS?
GROW UP!
YOU'RE CRANKY 'CAUSE MOMMY
AND DADDY SAID GOODBYE.
NO. I'M NOT.
OH. ADMIT IT. I
GET THE SAME WAY.
NO MATTER HOW OLD YOU ARE.
YOU NEVER LIKE TO
HEAR THEM SAY GOODBYE.
YEAH. I GUESS IT'S THAT FEAR
THAT YOU MIGHT
NEVER SEE THEM AGAIN.
BABY. YOU'LL SEE THEM AGAIN.
I KNOW. AND THE SICK THING IS
THAT I KIND OF MISS THEM.
I KIND OF DON'T.
DAN?
WHATY?
PULL MY FINGER.
AAH!
HI.
RIGHT. HERE'S THE DEAL.
I'LL GET THE CHECKBOOK OUT.
BUT I GOT TO WATCH.
WELL. WHAT A SURPRISE.
I'M NOT WORKING ON MY SHOW.
I THOUGHT I'D COME OVER.
CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY THE
NATIONAL CAPTIONING INSTITUTE. INC.
CAPTIONS COPYRIGHT 1989
CARSEY-WERNER PRODUCTIONS
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today